[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This plant can be used as a herbal medicine to treat gastric and intestinal problems, migraine, asthma, anemia, depression, anxiety and nervous ailments, among others.", "correct_answer": "Saint Johns Wort", "incorrect_answers": ["Tobacco", "Asafetida", "Cowhage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What will happen if a fork or a spoon falls on the ground according to Russian superstition?", "correct_answer": "A female guest will come.", "incorrect_answers": ["A male child will be born in the house.", "The person who dropped it will have to work very hard.", "The crops will be abundant."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of phobia does pilot Ted Striker have in the 1980 comedy movie Airplane!?", "correct_answer": "Fear of flying", "incorrect_answers": ["Fear of heights", "Fear of steering wheels", "Fear of women"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the donkey, voiced by Eddie Murphy, in the 2001 animated movie Shrek?", "correct_answer": "Donkey", "incorrect_answers": ["Edward", "Russel", "Thorn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The gravitational force on the surface of the Sun is greater than the gravitational force on Earths surface. If you weigh 180 lbs or 80 kg on Earth, what would your weight be on the Sun?", "correct_answer": "5022 lbs (2270 kg)", "incorrect_answers": ["440 lbs (200 kg)", "1100 lbs (500 kg)", "2770 lbs (1260 kg)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What distinction does Elise Raymonde Deroche hold?", "correct_answer": "She was the first female licensed pilot.", "incorrect_answers": ["She was the first female passenger in an airplane.", "She was the first female to fly a balloon.", "She was the first member of a royal house to fly in a plane."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Scary Movie film spoofed Scream, The 6th Sense, I Know What You Did Last Summer and Halloween?", "correct_answer": "Scary Movie", "incorrect_answers": ["Scary Movie 2", "Scary Movie 4", "Scary Movie 3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the characters from Steven Spielbergs 1975 movie Jaws was inspired by Captain Ahab from Herman Melvilles novel Moby-Dick?", "correct_answer": "Quint", "incorrect_answers": ["Mayor Larry Vaughn", "Martin Brody", "Matt Hooper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When George is feeding Bob Yappys dog treats in the movie UHF, what kind of cookies does he think he is feeding him?", "correct_answer": "Mrs. Hockenbergers butter cookies", "incorrect_answers": ["Mrs. Hockenmeyers butter cookies", "Mrs. Hockensens butter cookies", "Mrs. Hockenhousens butter cookies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the full name of the 33rd US President?", "correct_answer": "Harry S. Truman", "incorrect_answers": ["Harry Shine Truman", "Harry Simpson Truman", "Harry Simon Truman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This term refers to the organs that fill your abdominal cavity and chest.", "correct_answer": "viscera", "incorrect_answers": ["immune system", "circulatory system", "cementum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this American strategic life-simulation computer game you rule peoples lives. The game was developed by Maxis and published by Electronic Arts.", "correct_answer": "The Sims", "incorrect_answers": ["Call of Duty", "MaddenNFL", "StarCraft"]}]